Friends, today I am going to tell you about such a job in
which even if you are a fresher, you
can apply and earn very well sitting at home.
I will discuss the complete details with you in this video.
I have put the job link
in the description box.  You can check it from there and
apply quickly.
This job has come just a while ago.  So you must
watch this.  Apply.  If you have passed class 12th then
you can also apply.  And there is
no change in income and salary.
The more you work boldly, the better
money you will get.  I will discuss the complete details
in this video.  But friend, if you have
not subscribed to my channel then you will have to subscribe to the channel.  Be
sure to press the bell icon button so that you can get updates on this type of job
regularly.  I will try to make the
video as short as possible so that
you get maximum information in minimum time.
Ok?  You can see that
this is a vacancy from ICICI Psalm Life Insurance Company which has come just 19 hours ago.  The
head office is from Gorakhpur and is a
Kita.  If you want, you can do it part time also.  If
you want, you can do it full time.
So that's why there is no salary issue in this.
Then there is no strain.  If you want,
only if you do it full time then the salary will be
good.  If you reduce the good incentive
then the incentive will increase further and your
salary will increase. The people earning in this easily
earn up to Rs 40,500.  Ok
?  So you can see, friend,
you already know about ICICI.  This is our life
insurance policies, this is our company,
you have to sell it, you have to see
what is going on in the market and these are amazing
policies which you have to tell people,
you want good knowledge about the product, the
company should be with you, the
trading company will provide it to you, this is
a part time role for the insurance
agents, right, insurance agents will be
responsible for selling the range of the
insurance products, providing the
personal personalized financial advisors,
okay, so whatever our financial
advisors are, what type of
policy do people want, on what basis, nowadays every person is getting
SIPs done.  You see that every
person is investing money in mutual funds.  So
now they have to do this SIP according to the type of requirement.  Will
give them knowledge.  Ok?  So brother, what should you have in this
?  You should have proficiency
in insurance selling.  Meaning,
first of all you should have knowledge about
what this policy does?  What does this policy do
?  So if you are working part time and
you do some other work somewhere else and have
one or two hours left in the day, then you
can earn some money by working in that too.  Ok?
If you already have some
experience with insurance, that's a great
thing.  There is profit for you.
Understanding the financials and
applications, where and which
policies are giving you how much profit.
Ok?  So I will have to tell you all these things.
Customer Service Skills Including You must have
customer service skills.
You should have good relationship management skills.
You should be able to talk to 10 customers.
To work
independently and remotely so that you can
work well.  You can work remotely.  This
thing is proactive problem solving, you should get
certification.  Ok?  You should have
relevant certification and license in the
insurance. Plus, if you already have any such
certificate or
experience, then it will be beneficial for you.
Ok?  It is mentioned here that LM
Plus is a Bachelor's degree.  If you have any
preference in any of these fields, either from business or from final.  Ok
?  So this thing will be very good for you
and to apply you have to click on easy apply.
You can apply from here.
So friend, here you should not think
that we will do it tomorrow or the day after tomorrow.  The vacancy has just
come.  It is urgent that you apply it properly and get it
with a good brand, so
friend, I think you must have understood the information that I have
provided you.  Still,
make a bolder comment.
Less thank you in all the comments.  Thanks for watching my
video.  Please like share subscribe.  Thank
you.